Father,
when I was little,
you always liked teaching me how to fold paper.
But back then,
I was very clumsy
and never seemed to get it right.
Looking back now,
it doesn't seem so complicated after all.
Look.
Sui'er, watch carefully.
I'll teach you.
Fold and press.
Turn it over and do the same.
See?
A little folded bird
is done.
Have a try.
No, no.
It's too difficult.
I don't want to learn it.
Let me teach you.
Like this.
Look.
Fold and press.
Turn it over.
Like this.
Fold and press.
Dad.
Miss.
Here's the medicine for master.
Give it to me.
Father,
time to take the medicine.
I don't want to.
I...
No.
Father, you need to take the medicine.
Let me try.
Come on.
Minister Shen,
let's finish the medicine
before we play, okay?
Look,
there's a cricket here.
It's moving.
It's swimming.
Look.
Bitter.
I don't want to drink it.
I'm sorry, I don't want to drink it.
I'm sorry.
Sui'er.
Minister Shen.
Dad.
Dad, you're calling me.
You recognize me, Dad.
I'm sorry.
You remember me?
Father,
what do you remember?
What do you remember, father?
Father!
Don't worry.
Minister Shen
will recover.
Yes,
he will recover.
Your Highness,
why are you still up?
Physician Xue, the newly developed antidote
has been administered to Lord Shen.
It can temporarily
restore his consciousness.
Really?
Can you really cure my father?
Trust me,
no matter how long it takes,
I will definitely cure your father.
Thank you, Your Highness.
By the way,
has His Majesty said
how to deal with the Second Prince?
The Second Prince
has been imprisoned.
As for how to deal with him,
His Majesty has not decided yet.
That's right.
Even a tiger does not eat its own cubs.
let alone
His Majesty's beloved Prince.
But no matter what,
Prime Minister Shen
and Shen Residence
are under your protection.
And His Majesty also said
as long as Minister Shen recovers,
he can resume his position.
The moon is so round today.
Prince,
would you like to enjoy the moon with me?
Your Highness,
do you think
this case is closed?
Now,
we've only restored the innocence
of Prime Minister Shen and Xiao Wei.
Nothing else has been confirmed.
So, don't you think
the world is sometimes ridiculous?
They can easily
accuse innocent people
of wrongdoing,
but proving
the crimes
of the truly guilty
requires mountains of evidence.
This world is inherently unjust.
Xiao Wei...
Once dead, a person cannot be brought back.
Minister Shen
is mentally unstable.
It's reasonable for His Majesty
to make such a decision.
Your Highness,
as the case progresses to this point,
has it had any impact on you?
Could there be any implications?
Why do you ask?
I'm thinking,
after this case is closed,
you should go back to the border.
After you leave the capital this time,
maybe we will never
meet again in this life.
I can stay here.
If...
Your Highness
Tomorrow morning,
I'll take my father
back to the Prime Minister's Mansion for treatment.
Thank you
for taking care of me.
Would you like to
take off this mask for me?
Do you think
it can be taken off?
Your Highness
is the brother of His Majesty.
You are the Prince Yu with military power.
Even if I am willing to take it off,
is His Majesty willing to do so?
You just returned to the capital for a few days,
and you overthrew the Second Prince,
cleared my father's name.
If you stay in the capital,
even if His Majesty doesn't say it,
he will be more suspicious of you.
I'm afraid he will think
you came back to the capital this time
just to get involved in the court.
I don't care what my brother thinks,
I just want to ask you now,
are you willing to help me
take off this mask?
It's not that I don't want to,
but I can't.
It's late.
I'll go back and rest.
You are willing,
right?
My stupid brother
is no longer of value.
It's time to discard him.
What's
your next move?
Prince Yu has joined the game.
Then let him
get stuck in the mud
and can't get out.
Father.
Come here.
Su Bai.
Father.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Brother.
Father.
Our family is finally reunited.
Yes.
We're finally reunited.
My daughter,
you've suffered a lot.
Don't say that, father.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have married you off to Prince Rui.
I didn't take good care of you.
Father, don't say that.
It's all Mu Jinghao's fault.
It was him
who did those things
that led to this.
Sui'er.
The one in charge of this case
is Prince Yu, Mu Yunzheng.
Then,
the one who rode in the carriage with me
was him?
It was him.
I have something important to tell him.
Go get him back.
Prince Yu,
these are the crimes
of the Second Prince
I've been investigating for years.
It includes not only
his private alchemy workshop
and poisoning courtiers,
but also evidence of his intention to rebel.
Prime Minister Shen.
Minister Shen.
What happened to my father?
Father.
Sui'er,
nothing
is more important
than life.
Father,
I know.
You must live, father!
You must live!
Prime Minister Shen!
Dad!
Father!
Why?
Why is this happening?
Father!
Why?
Why hasn't anything changed?
Mu Jinghao!
It's Mu Jinghao who killed my father!
I'll kill him!
Sui'er!
Let me go!
Calm down!
I'm gonna kill him!
It's not the right time!
Why?
Why did my father still die?
Why couldn't I save him?
I can't change anything!
I can't do anything.
I've been waiting for you to kill me.
I didn't expect
you to kill my father.
Do you know why Shen Yi must die?
It's because
you keep spreading the evidence that
I made your father a fool.
I'm not afraid of him.
It's you.
It was you who forced me to kill him.
See?
My father never blamed me.
He never blamed me.
I just want to see justice done.
Fine.
Since you don't want justice,
I'll do it myself.
Shen Suhe,
how dare you!
Why not?
I should have killed you
when you killed all the people in the mansion.
I shouldn't have let you live.
Now,
I don't want you to die too easily.
My father wouldn't dare kill me.
How dare you kill me?
I know you are not ready to die.
So I don't plan to kill you now.
Last time,
you made my life a living hell.
And you're doing it again.
Fine.
If that's the case,
I'll make you experience
the agony of living.
Let's all suffer.
Shen Suhe,
you lunatic!
Wanna know what else
a lunatic can do?
Guess
where
I'll stab next.
Sui'er.
There are many ways to make life worse than death.
There's no need to dirty your hands.
Worse than death?
I'll teach you.
You sent someone to humiliate,
torture General Xiao,
and control him with drugs
to force a confession.
You made the entire army
suffer unjustly,
bearing the stain of treachery.
After the war,
those who survived
were unjustly punished,
and their families
were implicated.
Everything you've done to the border guards,
I'll repay you double.
I'll make you know
what is the real living hell.
Your Highness.
Chuchu.
His Majesty hasn't condemned you yet.
How dare you!
What's going on?
Your Majesty,
Consort Chu
has been kneeling outside the hall
for two days and nights,
asking to be imprisoned
to accompany Qian.
Today,
I happened to meet His Majesty,
and he
ordered me to bring her here.
Kneeling for two days and nights,
asking to be imprisoned to accompany him?
I didn't expect that
you're so loyal.
Don't be too proud.
When His Majesty makes up his mind,
and His Highness rises again,
he will definitely not let you go.
Rise again?
So you asked to be imprisoned
just to be his secondary consort
after he gets out of jail and rises again?
How dare you do this to her?
I'll report it to His Majesty.
Go ahead.
Warden,
although Ling Chuchu asked to accompany him,
the Second Prince committed
a serious crime.
It's better to
put her in the next cell.
Shen Suhe,
what do you mean?
Remember,
it's a permanent separation.
They must never meet again.
Do it!
Yes, Your Majesty.
My face, my face!
Ling Chuchu,
you'll never be the principal consort.
This cut
is my revenge.
Shen Suhe,
I'll kill you!
Take her away!
Yes.
Remember,
put her in a separate cell.
Jing Zhao,
just forget
what happened in the prison.
If His Majesty asks,
just say it was all my doing.
Understand?
Yes,
Your Majesty.
[Why does Zhao also have the ring?]
[Is it possible that Mu Jinghao]
[is not the one who strangled me?]